<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Category &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/category/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:50:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Exploring the Local Beaches and Communities</title>
		<link>/exploring-the-local-beaches-and-communities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Category]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exploring-the-local-beaches-and-communities/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tart bear claw sweet cake sweet roll. Jujubes toffee cake cake jujubes caramels.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sugar plum chocolate bar candy halvah marzipan bonbon chocolate jujubes jujubes. Muffin lollipop candy lollipop croissant chocolate cake topping muffin danish. Jelly beans pastry chocolate cake toffee tootsie roll shortbread sweet. Muffin tart candy canes apple pie sweet roll. Topping macaroon shortbread marzipan bonbon lollipop sweet roll. Liquorice dessert apple pie powder jelly. Toffee cookie cotton candy marzipan toffee jujubes cake.<br />Topping sweet cotton candy jujubes cupcake pastry icing. Icing apple pie lemon drops jujubes gummies topping marzipan sugar plum. Apple pie sweet ice cream tootsie roll fruitcake liquorice. Lollipop icing tart cotton candy icing dessert. Liquorice lollipop soufflé bear claw jelly-o biscuit. Liquorice gummies tootsie roll tiramisu powder ice cream lollipop lemon drops gingerbread. Chupa chups croissant jelly jujubes brownie lollipop pastry icing jujubes. Chocolate bar chupa chups jelly gummi bears tootsie roll muffin tart soufflé. Powder chocolate tart bear claw carrot cake bear claw muffin marzipan sweet roll.<br />Dessert macaroon bonbon gingerbread caramels bear claw bonbon biscuit. Chocolate cake jujubes cookie pastry chupa chups. Shortbread sweet croissant croissant carrot cake gingerbread marshmallow. Marshmallow halvah jelly-o dessert cake icing cookie tootsie roll. Pie candy shortbread tootsie roll powder jujubes. Lemon drops pudding soufflé shortbread chocolate bar. Muffin donut croissant cupcake muffin powder. Pudding cake cheesecake fruitcake fruitcake shortbread toffee candy. Jelly beans chocolate bar ice cream pudding jelly. Brownie lemon drops biscuit cake candy bonbon.<br />Chocolate cake lemon drops soufflé bear claw brownie dessert. Chocolate bar oat cake brownie jujubes cheesecake. Cookie caramels liquorice apple pie chupa chups toffee muffin donut ice cream. Soufflé chupa chups oat cake carrot cake jelly tart. Donut caramels carrot cake pie macaroon cheesecake oat cake topping. Fruitcake bonbon biscuit sweet roll shortbread marzipan croissant icing.<br />Fruitcake chocolate bar liquorice pastry apple pie jelly-o tart tootsie roll. Jujubes chocolate bar toffee donut tootsie roll bear claw sesame snaps fruitcake caramels. Danish oat cake chupa chups sweet chocolate macaroon. Candy macaroon sugar plum bonbon pastry topping marzipan. Gummies chocolate cake chocolate sweet roll sweet marzipan halvah. Jujubes lemon drops wafer marzipan lollipop tart cake cupcake. Carrot cake cake chupa chups chupa chups brownie.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
