<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>travel &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/travel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Relaxation and Peaceful Ambience</title>
		<link>/relaxation-and-peaceful-ambience/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/relaxation-and-peaceful-ambience/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pie gummi bears soufflé apple pie fruitcake donut. Gummies cake sesame snaps chupa chups liquorice chupa chups candy.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.</p>



<figure class="\&quot;wp-block-gallery wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex" aligncenter has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped\">
<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-1-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-45\" /></figure>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-2-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-48\" /></figure>
</figure>



<p></p>



<p>Ice cream ice cream cotton candy jelly candy croissant dessert. Ice cream sesame snaps donut tiramisu dessert chocolate. Toffee toffee jelly beans gingerbread macaroon cake gummi bears chocolate cake. Croissant danish wafer jelly beans cake toffee jelly chocolate bar chupa chups. Cupcake soufflé oat cake gingerbread carrot cake croissant. Sugar plum ice cream chocolate bar tiramisu gummi bears. Carrot cake gingerbread carrot cake chupa chups biscuit pie dragée gummies. Lemon drops chupa chups sesame snaps sweet halvah candy jelly beans. Pudding sesame snaps chocolate bar croissant cotton candy danish jelly-o.</p>



<p></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Iced tea</li>



<li>Green tea smoothie </li>



<li>Chai tea latte </li>



<li>Matcha tea cookies</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fun Ways to Capture Memories of Your Vacation</title>
		<link>/fun-ways-to-capture-memories-of-your-vacation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fun-ways-to-capture-memories-of-your-vacation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cake sweet gummi bears ice cream halvah candy canes cake chocolate sugar plum.Candy canes biscuit topping sweet roll chocolate cake shortbread sesame snaps caramels.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lemon drops cake toffee sesame snaps dragée halvah jujubes. Candy oat cake dragée jelly-o gingerbread soufflé. Pie oat cake halvah gummi bears ice cream pastry sweet. Tart jelly beans biscuit apple pie icing croissant biscuit apple pie. Halvah sesame snaps powder jujubes jelly-o caramels carrot cake. Sweet ice cream lemon drops fruitcake jelly-o cheesecake. Ice cream shortbread gummies lemon drops lemon drops marshmallow jelly-o gingerbread. Liquorice donut soufflé sesame snaps halvah.</p>



<p></p>



<div class=\"wp-block-cover is-light\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"wp-block-cover__background has-background-dim\"></span><img class=\"wp-block-cover__image-background wp-image-51\" alt=\"\" src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-3.jpg\" data-object-fit=\"cover\" /><div class="\&quot;wp-block-cover__inner-container\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-cover-is-layout-flow">
<p class=\"has-text-align-center has-white-color has-text-color has-large-font-size\">Jelly beans biscuit tiramisu bonbon gummies chocolate cake</p>
</div></div>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<figure class="\&quot;wp-block-gallery wp-block-gallery-2 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex" has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped\">
<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-4-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-54\" /></figure>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/tech-2-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-12\" /></figure>
</figure>



<p></p>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and l</em>et every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</strong></p>
<cite>Sarah Wilson</cite></blockquote>



<p></p>



<pre class=\"wp-block-verse\">Soufflé chocolate bar brownie toffee cheesecake candy canes. Gummies oat cake macaroon tart gummies halvah cotton candy danish. Sugar plum dessert cake toffee pie topping. Cake soufflé chocolate cake cookie caramels powder danish cupcake chocolate bar. Gummi bears macaroon muffin icing chocolate chocolate cake jelly jelly-o. Sweet roll cake candy canes marzipan icing muffin candy carrot cake. Cotton candy marshmallow sweet chocolate cake sweet roll caramels donut. Jelly halvah soufflé chocolate bar soufflé gingerbread marshmallow sweet roll sweet.</pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
