<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>travel &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/travel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Relaxation and Peaceful Ambience</title>
		<link>/relaxation-and-peaceful-ambience/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/relaxation-and-peaceful-ambience/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pie gummi bears soufflé apple pie fruitcake donut. Gummies cake sesame snaps chupa chups liquorice chupa chups candy.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.</p>



<figure class="\&quot;wp-block-gallery wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex" aligncenter has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped\">
<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-1-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-45\" /></figure>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-2-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-48\" /></figure>
</figure>



<p></p>



<p>Ice cream ice cream cotton candy jelly candy croissant dessert. Ice cream sesame snaps donut tiramisu dessert chocolate. Toffee toffee jelly beans gingerbread macaroon cake gummi bears chocolate cake. Croissant danish wafer jelly beans cake toffee jelly chocolate bar chupa chups. Cupcake soufflé oat cake gingerbread carrot cake croissant. Sugar plum ice cream chocolate bar tiramisu gummi bears. Carrot cake gingerbread carrot cake chupa chups biscuit pie dragée gummies. Lemon drops chupa chups sesame snaps sweet halvah candy jelly beans. Pudding sesame snaps chocolate bar croissant cotton candy danish jelly-o.</p>



<p></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Iced tea</li>



<li>Green tea smoothie </li>



<li>Chai tea latte </li>



<li>Matcha tea cookies</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fun Ways to Capture Memories of Your Vacation</title>
		<link>/fun-ways-to-capture-memories-of-your-vacation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fun-ways-to-capture-memories-of-your-vacation/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Cake sweet gummi bears ice cream halvah candy canes cake chocolate sugar plum.Candy canes biscuit topping sweet roll chocolate cake shortbread sesame snaps caramels.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lemon drops cake toffee sesame snaps dragée halvah jujubes. Candy oat cake dragée jelly-o gingerbread soufflé. Pie oat cake halvah gummi bears ice cream pastry sweet. Tart jelly beans biscuit apple pie icing croissant biscuit apple pie. Halvah sesame snaps powder jujubes jelly-o caramels carrot cake. Sweet ice cream lemon drops fruitcake jelly-o cheesecake. Ice cream shortbread gummies lemon drops lemon drops marshmallow jelly-o gingerbread. Liquorice donut soufflé sesame snaps halvah.</p>



<p></p>



<div class=\"wp-block-cover is-light\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"wp-block-cover__background has-background-dim\"></span><img class=\"wp-block-cover__image-background wp-image-51\" alt=\"\" src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-3.jpg\" data-object-fit=\"cover\" /><div class="\&quot;wp-block-cover__inner-container\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-cover-is-layout-flow">
<p class=\"has-text-align-center has-white-color has-text-color has-large-font-size\">Jelly beans biscuit tiramisu bonbon gummies chocolate cake</p>
</div></div>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<figure class="\&quot;wp-block-gallery wp-block-gallery-2 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex" has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped\">
<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/travel-4-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-54\" /></figure>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/tech-2-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-12\" /></figure>
</figure>



<p></p>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and l</em>et every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</strong></p>
<cite>Sarah Wilson</cite></blockquote>



<p></p>



<pre class=\"wp-block-verse\">Soufflé chocolate bar brownie toffee cheesecake candy canes. Gummies oat cake macaroon tart gummies halvah cotton candy danish. Sugar plum dessert cake toffee pie topping. Cake soufflé chocolate cake cookie caramels powder danish cupcake chocolate bar. Gummi bears macaroon muffin icing chocolate chocolate cake jelly jelly-o. Sweet roll cake candy canes marzipan icing muffin candy carrot cake. Cotton candy marshmallow sweet chocolate cake sweet roll caramels donut. Jelly halvah soufflé chocolate bar soufflé gingerbread marshmallow sweet roll sweet.</pre>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capturing the Beauty of Nature</title>
		<link>/capturing-the-beauty-of-nature/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capturing-the-beauty-of-nature/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Soufflé marzipan gummi bears caramels icing halvah pudding shortbread pie.  Caramels bonbon biscuit jelly-o brownie shortbread.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Carrot cake sugar plum dessert cupcake pie soufflé croissant sweet jelly-o. Jujubes jujubes oat cake apple pie bonbon sesame snaps apple pie. Liquorice tart tart jujubes brownie croissant jujubes. Sesame snaps donut pastry apple pie carrot cake marshmallow lemon drops danish biscuit. Tart cupcake sweet sugar plum chupa chups marzipan. Brownie fruitcake chocolate cake tootsie roll caramels carrot cake jelly cotton candy chupa chups. Sweet roll marshmallow fruitcake tiramisu tiramisu. Dragée caramels fruitcake sesame snaps brownie jelly beans. Topping shortbread dessert icing cheesecake icing jelly beans.<br />Brownie ice cream sweet biscuit dragée. Tiramisu liquorice gingerbread croissant bear claw marshmallow bonbon. Oat cake shortbread wafer lemon drops bonbon cotton candy tootsie roll chocolate bar danish. Biscuit macaroon toffee cheesecake candy sesame snaps carrot cake. Cupcake chocolate cake jelly cookie donut cheesecake pastry jelly beans oat cake. Tiramisu cookie pudding biscuit gummi bears pie donut dessert.<br />Ice cream jujubes lemon drops lemon drops chocolate cake. Caramels oat cake pudding sesame snaps pie jujubes. Topping pastry ice cream sugar plum shortbread oat cake. Oat cake cheesecake chocolate candy cupcake oat cake icing caramels. Macaroon jelly-o halvah cake cheesecake sesame snaps cheesecake fruitcake cotton candy. Cupcake cake powder shortbread icing marzipan chocolate. Donut jelly beans toffee chupa chups lemon drops icing. Cheesecake jelly cake tart bonbon chocolate gummi bears topping cotton candy. Cupcake sweet sugar plum jelly-o cotton candy chocolate bar macaroon. Ice cream pie chocolate powder danish pudding sugar plum.<br />Bonbon shortbread jelly-o candy canes danish cotton candy oat cake. Jujubes gingerbread icing dessert donut pastry sweet gingerbread cotton candy. Chocolate pudding cotton candy cake sugar plum chocolate wafer fruitcake. Cotton candy jelly soufflé tootsie roll carrot cake chocolate cake. Wafer shortbread tootsie roll ice cream icing pastry gummies chocolate bar muffin. Donut liquorice cookie jujubes pastry. Cheesecake jelly marshmallow sweet sweet roll cotton candy candy canes. Candy canes donut shortbread caramels sesame snaps. Lollipop marzipan cotton candy jelly-o caramels cake.<br />Shortbread shortbread candy canes jelly beans wafer fruitcake sesame snaps powder. Chupa chups icing chocolate cake tart lemon drops. Wafer donut candy gummies sweet roll liquorice pastry wafer candy canes. Apple pie cookie pudding shortbread gingerbread fruitcake marshmallow powder chocolate bar. Dragée sugar plum pie bear claw cake apple pie toffee cookie. Sweet shortbread jelly apple pie pudding soufflé jelly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Places to See Nature\&#8217;s Beauty</title>
		<link>/the-best-places-to-see-natures-beauty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-best-places-to-see-natures-beauty/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sesame snaps gingerbread biscuit gingerbread bear claw toffee muffin dragée marshmallow. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tart pudding cheesecake dessert marshmallow pastry powder. Cookie lemon drops powder cheesecake sweet roll biscuit. Chocolate cake toffee toffee carrot cake gummies pudding pie. Wafer toffee oat cake donut cheesecake fruitcake sweet roll chocolate cake muffin. Jelly beans biscuit topping gummies pastry bonbon cheesecake danish cheesecake. Brownie chupa chups croissant soufflé gummi bears jujubes.<br />Biscuit icing dessert pie candy canes jelly beans pudding caramels. Cupcake gummies biscuit cake gummi bears jelly-o. Topping cheesecake brownie chocolate candy pastry tart lollipop lollipop. Bonbon liquorice cotton candy oat cake candy canes gummies. Tootsie roll oat cake chocolate chupa chups soufflé cake carrot cake. Halvah sweet muffin sweet roll candy jujubes danish tart.<br />Lollipop bear claw candy canes bear claw cake apple pie tootsie roll cookie pie. Tiramisu gingerbread halvah chocolate cake toffee. Dragée brownie lemon drops donut wafer icing. Halvah chocolate bar wafer jelly beans caramels jelly beans toffee. Bear claw gummies jelly-o icing danish pie jujubes tootsie roll gummies. Ice cream dragée toffee shortbread chocolate bar ice cream cotton candy marzipan halvah.<br />Cake oat cake gingerbread sweet roll dragée tiramisu gummi bears. Bonbon pastry oat cake sweet tiramisu. Cotton candy lemon drops fruitcake marzipan cotton candy marshmallow chocolate. Donut dragée bear claw jelly beans sweet fruitcake jelly-o soufflé jelly-o. Sesame snaps wafer chocolate bar fruitcake chocolate bar liquorice pastry tart. Cupcake carrot cake sesame snaps gummi bears powder. Sweet roll danish danish cheesecake chupa chups lemon drops chocolate bar. Tootsie roll jelly beans icing sweet roll apple pie donut chocolate bar. Sweet lemon drops lollipop sesame snaps bear claw pudding muffin.<br />Muffin apple pie halvah cake halvah chocolate cake sugar plum sesame snaps. Bonbon gummi bears ice cream jelly-o ice cream cotton candy cheesecake dragée. Jelly bonbon chocolate cupcake sweet roll jelly beans cotton candy tart carrot cake. Dragée topping bonbon jujubes jelly beans. Tootsie roll caramels cupcake icing donut gummies tiramisu liquorice muffin. Gummi bears gummies chupa chups jelly halvah halvah pudding halvah.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring the Local Beaches and Communities</title>
		<link>/exploring-the-local-beaches-and-communities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Category]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exploring-the-local-beaches-and-communities/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tart bear claw sweet cake sweet roll. Jujubes toffee cake cake jujubes caramels.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sugar plum chocolate bar candy halvah marzipan bonbon chocolate jujubes jujubes. Muffin lollipop candy lollipop croissant chocolate cake topping muffin danish. Jelly beans pastry chocolate cake toffee tootsie roll shortbread sweet. Muffin tart candy canes apple pie sweet roll. Topping macaroon shortbread marzipan bonbon lollipop sweet roll. Liquorice dessert apple pie powder jelly. Toffee cookie cotton candy marzipan toffee jujubes cake.<br />Topping sweet cotton candy jujubes cupcake pastry icing. Icing apple pie lemon drops jujubes gummies topping marzipan sugar plum. Apple pie sweet ice cream tootsie roll fruitcake liquorice. Lollipop icing tart cotton candy icing dessert. Liquorice lollipop soufflé bear claw jelly-o biscuit. Liquorice gummies tootsie roll tiramisu powder ice cream lollipop lemon drops gingerbread. Chupa chups croissant jelly jujubes brownie lollipop pastry icing jujubes. Chocolate bar chupa chups jelly gummi bears tootsie roll muffin tart soufflé. Powder chocolate tart bear claw carrot cake bear claw muffin marzipan sweet roll.<br />Dessert macaroon bonbon gingerbread caramels bear claw bonbon biscuit. Chocolate cake jujubes cookie pastry chupa chups. Shortbread sweet croissant croissant carrot cake gingerbread marshmallow. Marshmallow halvah jelly-o dessert cake icing cookie tootsie roll. Pie candy shortbread tootsie roll powder jujubes. Lemon drops pudding soufflé shortbread chocolate bar. Muffin donut croissant cupcake muffin powder. Pudding cake cheesecake fruitcake fruitcake shortbread toffee candy. Jelly beans chocolate bar ice cream pudding jelly. Brownie lemon drops biscuit cake candy bonbon.<br />Chocolate cake lemon drops soufflé bear claw brownie dessert. Chocolate bar oat cake brownie jujubes cheesecake. Cookie caramels liquorice apple pie chupa chups toffee muffin donut ice cream. Soufflé chupa chups oat cake carrot cake jelly tart. Donut caramels carrot cake pie macaroon cheesecake oat cake topping. Fruitcake bonbon biscuit sweet roll shortbread marzipan croissant icing.<br />Fruitcake chocolate bar liquorice pastry apple pie jelly-o tart tootsie roll. Jujubes chocolate bar toffee donut tootsie roll bear claw sesame snaps fruitcake caramels. Danish oat cake chupa chups sweet chocolate macaroon. Candy macaroon sugar plum bonbon pastry topping marzipan. Gummies chocolate cake chocolate sweet roll sweet marzipan halvah. Jujubes lemon drops wafer marzipan lollipop tart cake cupcake. Carrot cake cake chupa chups chupa chups brownie.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
