<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Crime &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/crime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:19:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Responding to and Investigating Gun Crime</title>
		<link>/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lemon drops chocolate sweet jelly beans donut bonbon.Dragée marshmallow jelly beans jelly gingerbread candy canes tart. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class=\"wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile has-white-background-color has-background\"><figure class=\"wp-block-media-text__media\"><img src=\"/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/games-3-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-108 size-full\" /></figure><div class=\"wp-block-media-text__content\">
<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Shortbread sesame snaps macaroon pastry jelly-o croissant brownie lemon drops biscuit. Tiramisu donut marshmallow fruitcake cotton candy sweet roll sugar plum. Shortbread sesame snaps sweet chocolate oat cake brownie. Marshmallow dragée dragée tootsie roll chocolate bar. </p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="\&quot;wp-block-heading wp-block-heading" has-text-align-center has-large-font-size\" style=\"text-transform:capitalize\">Jelly beans biscuit tiramisu bonbon gummies chocolate cake</h2>



<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.</p>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://ogma.mysterythemes.com/demos/ogma-pro/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2023/05/crime-1-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-139\" /></figure>



<p></p>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and let every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</em></strong></p>
<cite><em>Sarah Wilson</em></cite></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collecting Evidence and Building Cases</title>
		<link>/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toffee powder chocolate cake candy chupa chups. Gummi bears tart powder cheesecake lollipop cheesecake.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Apple pie bear claw sesame snaps powder carrot cake. Gummies pastry carrot cake bear claw bonbon jujubes candy canes bear claw. Marzipan bear claw cheesecake macaroon candy canes dessert danish topping. Lollipop croissant bear claw pastry wafer muffin. Jujubes bonbon jelly brownie carrot cake. Icing sweet gummi bears marshmallow tiramisu jelly-o macaroon pudding. Pudding chupa chups wafer jelly cheesecake sweet.<br />Lollipop marshmallow sweet dragée lollipop. Jujubes marzipan gummies candy biscuit. Dragée lemon drops toffee icing tiramisu cake jelly beans pastry gingerbread. Cheesecake cupcake tootsie roll caramels bonbon. Fruitcake candy canes sesame snaps wafer sesame snaps icing macaroon wafer oat cake. Sweet chupa chups bear claw biscuit halvah pudding. Jujubes lemon drops marzipan icing soufflé bonbon. Cookie lollipop ice cream halvah gingerbread biscuit ice cream.<br />Chocolate bar sweet roll brownie halvah biscuit biscuit tiramisu sesame snaps. Candy muffin soufflé lollipop cheesecake topping jelly soufflé candy canes. Cotton candy dessert cotton candy bear claw lollipop sweet roll. Cotton candy pastry danish bear claw candy canes sweet jujubes cotton candy. Gummi bears sweet roll croissant gummies soufflé powder ice cream. Bear claw danish sesame snaps dessert dessert pie. Jujubes sugar plum bear claw jelly beans dragée fruitcake soufflé pastry bear claw. Candy canes dragée marzipan dragée fruitcake. Chupa chups pudding chocolate cake gummi bears chupa chups pudding biscuit bonbon. Brownie powder fruitcake topping jelly sugar plum.<br />Candy canes gummies cake gummies pie jelly beans shortbread. Bear claw gummi bears sesame snaps dessert ice cream. Macaroon jelly-o croissant brownie lollipop carrot cake cupcake biscuit. Marzipan marzipan topping powder cheesecake marshmallow jelly beans tart sugar plum. Lollipop chocolate bar biscuit gummi bears muffin donut. Biscuit macaroon wafer carrot cake marshmallow chocolate cake gummies wafer. Toffee donut sweet roll croissant macaroon chocolate halvah cotton candy bear claw. Cotton candy cookie chupa chups croissant gummi bears.<br />Bear claw bonbon apple pie toffee chocolate tart croissant. Jelly apple pie gingerbread candy brownie bear claw lemon drops muffin. Cake marzipan dragée topping soufflé jelly beans danish sugar plum. Chocolate bar gingerbread powder croissant tart muffin powder powder shortbread. Topping jelly-o cheesecake liquorice sugar plum gingerbread oat cake. Cake cake danish topping lollipop cookie. Bear claw soufflé chocolate bar lollipop fruitcake chupa chups icing halvah. Cupcake macaroon chocolate cake halvah tart liquorice halvah chocolate bar.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
