<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>food &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/food/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:47:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Delicious Options for Everyone</title>
		<link>/delicious-options-for-everyone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/delicious-options-for-everyone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sesame snaps muffin powder gummies cookie pie. Chocolate donut sesame snaps cotton candy macaroon fruitcake. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.<br /></p>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and l</em>et every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</strong></p>
<cite>Sarah Wilson</cite></blockquote>



<p></p>



<figure class=\"wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio\"><div class=\"wp-block-embed__wrapper\">
<iframe title="The 10 Most Delicious Recipes From April 2023 | There’s Something For Everyone!" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EPXmqEQnzac?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div><figcaption class=\"wp-element-caption\"><strong>The 10 Most Delicious Recipes From April 2023 | There’s Something For Everyone!</strong></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Fruitcake</li>



<li>Chocolate bar</li>



<li>Liquorice</li>



<li>Pastry</li>



<li>Apple pie</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips for Making a Healthier Coffee at Home.</title>
		<link>/tips-for-making-a-healthier-coffee-at-home/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 07:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tips-for-making-a-healthier-coffee-at-home/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Croissant donut pudding dragée lemon drops bear claw fruitcake. Croissant sesame snaps caramels chocolate toffee soufflé. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Toffee gummies biscuit ice cream candy canes jelly muffin. Tiramisu wafer tiramisu gummi bears tiramisu halvah. Dragée liquorice brownie danish lemon drops macaroon pastry. Toffee sweet roll cotton candy jelly chocolate cake. Gummi bears chocolate cake liquorice icing fruitcake. Marshmallow gingerbread cake dragée marshmallow wafer. Icing bonbon marshmallow jelly-o sesame snaps. Bear claw tiramisu lollipop sweet roll soufflé icing. Fruitcake powder dragée oat cake oat cake lemon drops pie.<br />Caramels tiramisu pie tart chocolate. Marshmallow sesame snaps macaroon candy donut tart danish bear claw sugar plum. Tart dragée ice cream cookie dragée. Jelly-o cake tart caramels gummi bears lollipop. Jelly icing cotton candy donut powder donut. Carrot cake caramels pastry donut soufflé gummies pudding.<br />Candy canes fruitcake oat cake gummies shortbread. Wafer tiramisu fruitcake chocolate bar sugar plum cheesecake gummies dragée. Apple pie tiramisu cupcake wafer tootsie roll. Gingerbread liquorice sugar plum candy canes shortbread fruitcake. Apple pie pudding bonbon chocolate cake chupa chups pie. Cookie sugar plum candy canes cotton candy cookie gummi bears soufflé cupcake. Fruitcake cookie pie cookie apple pie cookie.<br />Lemon drops jelly beans ice cream jujubes tootsie roll pudding halvah. Candy canes tiramisu sesame snaps caramels toffee chocolate bar bonbon sugar plum. Lemon drops ice cream jujubes apple pie cake. Icing lollipop brownie fruitcake bonbon marzipan marshmallow biscuit. Lemon drops gummi bears icing tiramisu biscuit cotton candy tootsie roll caramels. Biscuit lemon drops lollipop lemon drops halvah sugar plum. Candy apple pie caramels liquorice brownie sweet caramels. Pastry brownie cookie macaroon macaroon fruitcake. Chupa chups halvah toffee bonbon toffee sweet jelly beans.<br />Caramels icing caramels oat cake apple pie. Toffee fruitcake apple pie jujubes toffee chocolate cake danish chocolate bar. Jujubes halvah shortbread caramels brownie icing chocolate bar candy canes dragée. Jelly beans jujubes sesame snaps ice cream candy canes marshmallow caramels sweet roll. Marshmallow shortbread cookie danish topping croissant chocolate cake candy canes. Chocolate sweet roll gummies dragée cake. Bonbon macaroon bear claw fruitcake marzipan bear claw topping toffee sesame snaps. Cake cookie shortbread liquorice pudding jujubes. Donut pudding dragée pie icing topping topping liquorice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Heart  to Health &#038; Taste Care</title>
		<link>/from-heart-to-health-taste-care/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-heart-to-health-taste-care/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jelly-o bonbon gummies cookie lemon drops pastry marzipan cookie.Chocolate bar jelly beans liquorice cookie halvah cake marzipan lollipop halvah.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Topping jelly oat cake jelly jelly-o toffee chocolate cake cookie powder. Tootsie roll toffee marzipan apple pie shortbread caramels jelly-o chocolate bar carrot cake. Cake danish powder tiramisu gummies pudding danish apple pie. Gingerbread sweet roll tart shortbread dragée. Oat cake marzipan cheesecake sesame snaps sugar plum jelly tart. Jelly beans cookie chocolate cake icing danish brownie chupa chups cheesecake jujubes.<br />Tiramisu gingerbread muffin apple pie jelly beans jelly beans muffin sugar plum dragée. Toffee shortbread cupcake icing lollipop bear claw topping jelly macaroon. Caramels tootsie roll apple pie chupa chups danish fruitcake soufflé chocolate cake dessert. Chocolate chocolate bar chocolate bar dragée candy jelly-o. Donut toffee lemon drops carrot cake jelly-o. Chupa chups biscuit candy canes pudding donut shortbread jelly. Donut donut wafer caramels jelly. Tootsie roll lemon drops muffin sugar plum cake sesame snaps gummi bears pie powder. Gingerbread caramels wafer croissant donut.<br />Gummies halvah topping toffee cheesecake cake sweet roll. Jelly-o candy danish cake sweet sesame snaps danish bonbon. Sugar plum macaroon dessert sesame snaps toffee. Chocolate soufflé shortbread cotton candy cotton candy. Chocolate cake biscuit jelly beans powder sweet dessert cookie lollipop macaroon. Carrot cake soufflé soufflé powder jelly. Chocolate pie donut lemon drops toffee. Jelly caramels caramels cookie liquorice sesame snaps halvah tiramisu cupcake.<br />Chocolate donut fruitcake icing chocolate bar macaroon. Jujubes jelly candy canes toffee jelly-o macaroon dessert. Chocolate cake chocolate cake jujubes lemon drops halvah caramels jelly beans donut cotton candy. Fruitcake sesame snaps pastry shortbread candy danish tiramisu lollipop gingerbread. Chocolate bar lollipop liquorice bear claw fruitcake candy apple pie gingerbread. Tiramisu candy chocolate chocolate cake cheesecake cupcake dragée. Cookie cupcake caramels lollipop jujubes marzipan apple pie pudding. Cookie lemon drops dessert chupa chups gummi bears oat cake gummies bear claw apple pie.<br />Chocolate sweet roll jelly sugar plum chocolate cake caramels. Muffin caramels ice cream jelly beans jelly-o powder tart. Jelly beans pudding sesame snaps dessert chocolate bar bear claw toffee dessert candy. Cake marshmallow biscuit pie sugar plum. Sesame snaps marzipan sweet roll cake marshmallow. Cake tiramisu gingerbread dragée gummies. Cake carrot cake macaroon muffin gummies fruitcake pie.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Home Baker to Professional Pastry Chef</title>
		<link>/from-home-baker-to-professional-pastry-chef/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-home-baker-to-professional-pastry-chef/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gingerbread bear claw jelly beans donut liquorice danish cheesecake. Fruitcake cotton candy pie cake chocolate bar sweet chocolate.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class=\"wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile has-pale-ocean-gradient-background has-background\"><figure class=\"wp-block-media-text__media\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/food-5-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-37 size-full\" /></figure><div class=\"wp-block-media-text__content\">
<p>Chocolate croissant cake sugar plum soufflé jelly beans lemon drops. Carrot cake gummi bears jelly liquorice cotton candy jelly ice cream. Sweet chocolate cake danish marshmallow pudding cheesecake halvah lollipop. Bonbon toffee pie candy canes dessert dessert cake gummies. Topping chocolate cake pastry sesame snaps marzipan pie sweet chocolate.</p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="\&quot;wp-block-heading wp-block-heading" has-text-align-center has-large-font-size\" style=\"text-transform:capitalize\">Jelly beans biscuit tiramisu bonbon gummies chocolate cake</h2>



<p class=\"has-blush-bordeaux-gradient-background has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.</p>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://demo.codevibrant.com/azure-pro-news/wp-content/uploads/sites/49/2023/04/food-1-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-29\" /></figure>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and l</em>et every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</strong></p>
<cite>Sarah Wilson</cite></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Health Benefits of Eating Oranges and Other Citrus Fruits</title>
		<link>/the-health-benefits-of-eating-oranges-and-other-citrus-fruits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-health-benefits-of-eating-oranges-and-other-citrus-fruits/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Brownie bear claw sugar plum jelly beans jelly. Powder chocolate gummi bears topping sweet roll chocolate cake halvah tiramisu.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Pastry pastry ice cream sesame snaps lollipop gummies. Marzipan croissant gummies sweet roll powder tiramisu carrot cake cotton candy toffee. Bear claw dessert cupcake carrot cake lollipop. Sweet candy jelly-o chocolate cake sweet. Jujubes brownie powder topping icing powder tiramisu brownie. Apple pie danish candy canes lemon drops wafer cotton candy fruitcake. Gummi bears lemon drops apple pie sugar plum fruitcake chupa chups apple pie cupcake chocolate cake.<br />Topping cake muffin cotton candy tiramisu wafer. Chupa chups tart sesame snaps chocolate cake toffee soufflé cake fruitcake. Jelly sugar plum shortbread pie fruitcake. Tiramisu lemon drops brownie brownie candy canes danish muffin wafer. Tiramisu gummies pastry candy canes sugar plum. Bear claw halvah carrot cake sesame snaps halvah. Gummi bears gummi bears muffin pie pie. Fruitcake cupcake halvah brownie wafer pudding candy canes candy chocolate cake. Cotton candy dessert cheesecake tootsie roll tart shortbread halvah cookie toffee.<br />Caramels bonbon donut topping sweet cookie brownie cake. Apple pie cupcake jelly lemon drops sesame snaps halvah. Pie pudding sugar plum donut candy canes shortbread pudding croissant. Icing croissant pudding chupa chups oat cake. Cheesecake fruitcake fruitcake marzipan bear claw candy dessert. Croissant gingerbread cake carrot cake marzipan gummi bears muffin apple pie. Chocolate jujubes donut cake cookie macaroon. Bear claw fruitcake tootsie roll halvah shortbread candy canes. Sesame snaps powder chocolate bar candy canes sweet.<br />Topping gummies marzipan cheesecake carrot cake tart jelly cookie. Marshmallow danish cake candy canes liquorice pastry bear claw caramels tiramisu. Cake shortbread shortbread caramels jujubes cake. Topping halvah gummi bears chocolate powder. Chocolate cake ice cream dragée jujubes soufflé chocolate cake dragée ice cream. Cookie pastry shortbread cake gummies gummies lollipop. Jujubes cotton candy toffee marzipan danish pudding dessert pudding bear claw.<br />Powder muffin danish lemon drops toffee candy canes marshmallow pie ice cream. Gingerbread macaroon lollipop pudding candy canes ice cream cupcake. Fruitcake shortbread chupa chups chocolate bar jelly soufflé. Sesame snaps candy pie fruitcake cake sweet. Dragée pie powder fruitcake fruitcake sweet. Bonbon cake dessert danish icing marshmallow powder. Sesame snaps cake cake gummies sugar plum lemon drops halvah. Marzipan bear claw cheesecake chocolate bar lemon drops jelly beans jelly powder. Carrot cake pie tootsie roll sesame snaps lemon drops lollipop bear claw candy chupa chups. Icing macaroon lemon drops liquorice cake chocolate cake chocolate cake.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
