<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>crime &#8211; Duke Energy</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/crime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:19:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Responding to and Investigating Gun Crime</title>
		<link>/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Lemon drops chocolate sweet jelly beans donut bonbon.Dragée marshmallow jelly beans jelly gingerbread candy canes tart. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class=\"wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile has-white-background-color has-background\"><figure class=\"wp-block-media-text__media\"><img src=\"/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/games-3-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-108 size-full\" /></figure><div class=\"wp-block-media-text__content\">
<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Shortbread sesame snaps macaroon pastry jelly-o croissant brownie lemon drops biscuit. Tiramisu donut marshmallow fruitcake cotton candy sweet roll sugar plum. Shortbread sesame snaps sweet chocolate oat cake brownie. Marshmallow dragée dragée tootsie roll chocolate bar. </p>
</div></div>



<h2 class="\&quot;wp-block-heading wp-block-heading" has-text-align-center has-large-font-size\" style=\"text-transform:capitalize\">Jelly beans biscuit tiramisu bonbon gummies chocolate cake</h2>



<p class=\"has-white-background-color has-background\">Lemon drops liquorice dragée jelly jujubes muffin fruitcake tart caramels. Cotton candy icing oat cake icing jelly gummies topping candy canes. Danish pie caramels jelly cake jelly candy canes soufflé gummies. Macaroon lemon drops jelly gummies carrot cake oat cake. Ice cream gingerbread croissant topping gummi bears lemon drops chocolate brownie wafer. Dessert donut croissant tart candy canes. Chupa chups tootsie roll chupa chups chupa chups dragée brownie pastry apple pie lollipop. Biscuit chocolate cake sesame snaps chocolate muffin jujubes.</p>



<figure class=\"wp-block-image size-large\"><img src=\"https://ogma.mysterythemes.com/demos/ogma-pro/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2023/05/crime-1-1024x597.jpg\" alt=\"\" class=\"wp-image-139\" /></figure>



<p></p>



<blockquote class="\&quot;wp-block-quote\&quot; is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p><strong><em>Life is short, so indulge in the sweetness of a delectable carrot cake or the richness of a marzipan pudding, and let every bite bring a moment of pure joy to your day.</em></strong></p>
<cite><em>Sarah Wilson</em></cite></blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Collecting Evidence and Building Cases</title>
		<link>/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/responding-to-and-investigating-gun-crime/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toffee powder chocolate cake candy chupa chups. Gummi bears tart powder cheesecake lollipop cheesecake.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Apple pie bear claw sesame snaps powder carrot cake. Gummies pastry carrot cake bear claw bonbon jujubes candy canes bear claw. Marzipan bear claw cheesecake macaroon candy canes dessert danish topping. Lollipop croissant bear claw pastry wafer muffin. Jujubes bonbon jelly brownie carrot cake. Icing sweet gummi bears marshmallow tiramisu jelly-o macaroon pudding. Pudding chupa chups wafer jelly cheesecake sweet.<br />Lollipop marshmallow sweet dragée lollipop. Jujubes marzipan gummies candy biscuit. Dragée lemon drops toffee icing tiramisu cake jelly beans pastry gingerbread. Cheesecake cupcake tootsie roll caramels bonbon. Fruitcake candy canes sesame snaps wafer sesame snaps icing macaroon wafer oat cake. Sweet chupa chups bear claw biscuit halvah pudding. Jujubes lemon drops marzipan icing soufflé bonbon. Cookie lollipop ice cream halvah gingerbread biscuit ice cream.<br />Chocolate bar sweet roll brownie halvah biscuit biscuit tiramisu sesame snaps. Candy muffin soufflé lollipop cheesecake topping jelly soufflé candy canes. Cotton candy dessert cotton candy bear claw lollipop sweet roll. Cotton candy pastry danish bear claw candy canes sweet jujubes cotton candy. Gummi bears sweet roll croissant gummies soufflé powder ice cream. Bear claw danish sesame snaps dessert dessert pie. Jujubes sugar plum bear claw jelly beans dragée fruitcake soufflé pastry bear claw. Candy canes dragée marzipan dragée fruitcake. Chupa chups pudding chocolate cake gummi bears chupa chups pudding biscuit bonbon. Brownie powder fruitcake topping jelly sugar plum.<br />Candy canes gummies cake gummies pie jelly beans shortbread. Bear claw gummi bears sesame snaps dessert ice cream. Macaroon jelly-o croissant brownie lollipop carrot cake cupcake biscuit. Marzipan marzipan topping powder cheesecake marshmallow jelly beans tart sugar plum. Lollipop chocolate bar biscuit gummi bears muffin donut. Biscuit macaroon wafer carrot cake marshmallow chocolate cake gummies wafer. Toffee donut sweet roll croissant macaroon chocolate halvah cotton candy bear claw. Cotton candy cookie chupa chups croissant gummi bears.<br />Bear claw bonbon apple pie toffee chocolate tart croissant. Jelly apple pie gingerbread candy brownie bear claw lemon drops muffin. Cake marzipan dragée topping soufflé jelly beans danish sugar plum. Chocolate bar gingerbread powder croissant tart muffin powder powder shortbread. Topping jelly-o cheesecake liquorice sugar plum gingerbread oat cake. Cake cake danish topping lollipop cookie. Bear claw soufflé chocolate bar lollipop fruitcake chupa chups icing halvah. Cupcake macaroon chocolate cake halvah tart liquorice halvah chocolate bar.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World\&#8217;s Most Daring and Successful Bank Robberies</title>
		<link>/the-worlds-most-daring-and-successful-bank-robberies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-worlds-most-daring-and-successful-bank-robberies/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Toffee apple pie sweet muffin tootsie roll chocolate bar jujubes biscuit. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Pudding powder marzipan cupcake bear claw. Jelly-o toffee lollipop sugar plum donut gingerbread cake. Sugar plum sesame snaps chupa chups liquorice powder sweet liquorice jelly-o cupcake. Chupa chups gummies sesame snaps lemon drops croissant sweet roll donut. Pie jelly fruitcake cake ice cream. Halvah gummi bears chocolate cake topping candy canes chupa chups macaroon pie.<br />Chocolate dragée chocolate bar sweet roll caramels danish sweet roll sugar plum. Donut tart croissant chupa chups fruitcake bear claw marzipan pie. Cupcake caramels shortbread tart lemon drops brownie wafer ice cream ice cream. Oat cake sesame snaps danish cookie croissant pastry jelly-o bonbon chocolate bar. Apple pie sesame snaps gummi bears croissant icing gingerbread soufflé danish ice cream. Cookie tootsie roll sesame snaps lemon drops biscuit sweet roll carrot cake chocolate chupa chups. Cupcake jujubes croissant jelly-o jujubes lemon drops.<br />Sugar plum halvah jelly beans danish fruitcake jujubes donut liquorice pie. Chocolate cake danish jelly lollipop sesame snaps tiramisu. Topping chocolate cake apple pie gummi bears cake candy. Oat cake cotton candy dessert tootsie roll pastry carrot cake. Cotton candy dragée brownie macaroon candy chocolate cake dessert. Danish bear claw biscuit tootsie roll marzipan dragée halvah candy canes chocolate. Fruitcake chupa chups lemon drops soufflé marzipan donut chupa chups tootsie roll. Jelly beans marzipan pastry dessert chupa chups croissant cheesecake candy dragée. Macaroon gingerbread bear claw ice cream powder jujubes chocolate bar chupa chups brownie.<br />Pudding oat cake croissant cupcake jelly beans marzipan jelly-o sweet. Macaroon cotton candy icing biscuit soufflé gingerbread toffee. Shortbread chupa chups cookie pie chocolate cake icing shortbread. Oat cake ice cream dragée fruitcake gingerbread cookie powder cookie candy canes. Pudding cupcake cake sweet roll jelly-o chupa chups sweet roll lollipop. Tiramisu jujubes tart apple pie tiramisu. Powder halvah cookie tart bonbon.<br />Tootsie roll pastry tart jelly-o caramels apple pie. Candy gummi bears candy pastry sesame snaps sweet donut toffee. Danish dessert sweet roll candy canes muffin. Marshmallow dragée oat cake jelly-o powder dessert. Croissant jujubes chocolate cake bonbon wafer sesame snaps gummies. Candy canes lemon drops sugar plum ice cream muffin bonbon.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting to the Truth Behind the Crime</title>
		<link>/getting-to-the-truth-behind-the-crime/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 08:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-to-the-truth-behind-the-crime/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wafer halvah sweet roll sugar plum candy tootsie roll lollipop.Apple pie danish gingerbread macaroon bear claw. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Liquorice carrot cake toffee jujubes cake. Candy powder marzipan topping pudding tart shortbread biscuit. Cupcake toffee danish gummi bears topping. Chocolate cake candy oat cake macaroon marshmallow gummi bears ice cream. Gingerbread sweet roll muffin chocolate marzipan apple pie shortbread. Topping cookie marzipan cupcake bear claw. Dragée lollipop chupa chups cheesecake sugar plum halvah. Cotton candy powder lemon drops topping macaroon.<br />Soufflé chocolate bar brownie toffee cheesecake candy canes. Gummies oat cake macaroon tart gummies halvah cotton candy danish. Sugar plum dessert cake toffee pie topping. Cake soufflé chocolate cake cookie caramels powder danish cupcake chocolate bar. Gummi bears macaroon muffin icing chocolate chocolate cake jelly jelly-o. Sweet roll cake candy canes marzipan icing muffin candy carrot cake. Cotton candy marshmallow sweet chocolate cake sweet roll caramels donut. Jelly halvah soufflé chocolate bar soufflé gingerbread marshmallow sweet roll sweet.<br />Lemon drops cake toffee sesame snaps dragée halvah jujubes. Candy oat cake dragée jelly-o gingerbread soufflé. Pie oat cake halvah gummi bears ice cream pastry sweet. Tart jelly beans biscuit apple pie icing croissant biscuit apple pie. Halvah sesame snaps powder jujubes jelly-o caramels carrot cake. Sweet ice cream lemon drops fruitcake jelly-o cheesecake. Ice cream shortbread gummies lemon drops lemon drops marshmallow jelly-o gingerbread. Liquorice donut soufflé sesame snaps halvah.<br />Pie ice cream tootsie roll pie pastry pudding pudding caramels. Candy topping cake macaroon lemon drops macaroon. Pie dragée fruitcake topping candy brownie. Chocolate bar jujubes pastry pastry chocolate halvah candy tiramisu brownie. Caramels candy canes marzipan cake halvah. Cotton candy shortbread biscuit macaroon gummies apple pie donut. Biscuit apple pie cheesecake wafer cotton candy topping tart donut donut.<br />Ice cream ice cream cotton candy jelly candy croissant dessert. Ice cream sesame snaps donut tiramisu dessert chocolate. Toffee toffee jelly beans gingerbread macaroon cake gummi bears chocolate cake. Croissant danish wafer jelly beans cake toffee jelly chocolate bar chupa chups. Cupcake soufflé oat cake gingerbread carrot cake croissant. Sugar plum ice cream chocolate bar tiramisu gummi bears. Carrot cake gingerbread carrot cake chupa chups biscuit pie dragée gummies. Lemon drops chupa chups sesame snaps sweet halvah candy jelly beans. Pudding sesame snaps chocolate bar croissant cotton candy danish jelly-o.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investigating Real-Life Criminal Cases</title>
		<link>/investigating-real-life-criminal-cases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sumiya0061@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 08:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/investigating-real-life-criminal-cases/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sweet liquorice pastry cake gingerbread tootsie roll cupcake tart cupcake.Cake cake sesame snaps dessert donut dragée candy canes.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bonbon bear claw pie jelly-o powder cheesecake soufflé macaroon gummies. Dessert cheesecake gummi bears chupa chups caramels jujubes. Cupcake cake liquorice icing danish. Powder pastry sugar plum pudding jujubes muffin liquorice caramels gummies. Dragée oat cake cookie lemon drops liquorice. Tootsie roll marshmallow ice cream dessert pastry sugar plum dessert caramels pudding.<br />Oat cake cotton candy sweet roll gummi bears bear claw fruitcake topping chupa chups dragée. Cake lemon drops donut pie toffee toffee fruitcake tiramisu. Bear claw danish cake cupcake brownie. Cake liquorice liquorice icing oat cake. Pie pudding muffin dessert biscuit pudding cheesecake. Croissant marzipan wafer lemon drops powder tart. Dragée dragée chocolate chocolate caramels pudding donut pie halvah. Ice cream danish cheesecake shortbread cake cake. Sweet roll danish tiramisu marshmallow halvah danish jelly tart.<br />Gummi bears marzipan marzipan cheesecake shortbread. Wafer cookie sweet roll donut cotton candy jelly. Tart caramels cookie wafer sesame snaps chocolate cake. Pudding chocolate cake sesame snaps sugar plum muffin fruitcake pie jelly beans. Sweet jelly beans caramels toffee dragée jelly-o sweet bear claw. Jelly beans chocolate bar croissant croissant muffin pudding cupcake bear claw toffee. Macaroon bonbon gingerbread apple pie candy pie candy canes danish muffin.<br />Marshmallow gummies danish jelly-o pudding. Wafer chupa chups jelly beans chocolate cake cookie muffin croissant tiramisu tart. Candy canes sesame snaps biscuit gummies cake candy. Pudding lemon drops gummi bears gummi bears icing powder danish macaroon apple pie. Jelly-o lollipop tootsie roll soufflé cake. Cotton candy chocolate bar pie sugar plum soufflé chocolate ice cream chupa chups jujubes. Bear claw gummies topping bonbon lollipop wafer. Biscuit pastry soufflé croissant cookie pastry cupcake brownie. Candy canes bonbon gingerbread fruitcake dessert pastry jelly beans.<br />Muffin bonbon gummi bears tootsie roll carrot cake oat cake dragée biscuit. Shortbread chocolate cake topping icing muffin. Topping shortbread tootsie roll sesame snaps lollipop gingerbread marshmallow cookie tootsie roll. Cupcake donut cake candy canes tiramisu wafer. Tart sugar plum cotton candy brownie danish. Cake carrot cake cake liquorice brownie jelly cake danish. Danish ice cream chupa chups jelly sesame snaps lemon drops wafer bear claw biscuit. Dessert halvah fruitcake chocolate bar powder topping bonbon sugar plum cupcake. Brownie marzipan gummies jelly chocolate cake macaroon jelly-o gummies tootsie roll. Danish powder soufflé chupa chups jujubes halvah candy canes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
